vncentral.com 2009-03-21

# VNCentral - An Online Social Community and Entertainment Company

**NOTICE**   
VNCentral will notify you when it is collecting personally identifiable information about you, as well as the use or uses VNCentral intends to make with such information. For example, we may need to collect information to respond to your requests for search results, buying products, requesting information, or to allow you to send or post messages, or for billing purposes. We also keep information about customers, individual shopping sessions, and purchases in a secure database on our servers in order to fulfill online transaction and banking requirements. 

**ANONYMOUS INFORMATION**  
We may collect certain non-personal information from your IP address. This information is used only to provide an enhanced on-line experience for our visitors by optimizing our Web pages for your computer (i.e., the identity of your Internet browser, IP address, referral data, platform type, and search terms ). We may also use this non-personal information to determine the total number of visitors to our Web Sitess. 

**USE OF COOKIES**  
When you view our Web Sites, we may store some information on your computer. This information will be in the form of a 'Cookie' and will help us in many ways. For example, Cookies allow us to tailor a Web Sites to better match your interests and preferences. With most Internet Browsers, you can erase Cookies from your computer hard drive, block all Cookies, or receive a warning before a Cookie is stored. Please refer to your Browser instructions or help screen to learn more about these functions. 

**THIRD PARTY ADVERTISMENTS**  
To try and bring you offers that are of interest to you, we have relationships with other companies that we allow to place ads on our Web pages. As a result of your visit to our site, ad server companies (such as Google's Adsense) may collect information such as your domain type, your IP address and clickstream information.   
* Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site.  
* Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet.  
* Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy.

**INFORMATION COLLECTED IN DELIVERY OF ADVERTISEMENTS**  
In the course of delivering an advertisement to VNCentral visitors, VNCentral, or its advertising agency, does not collect any personally-identifiable information about the Web Sites user, such as the user's name, address, phone number or email address. VNCentral' advertising agency does, however, collect non-personally identifiable information, such as the server a user's computer is logged onto, the user's browser type (for example, Netscape or Internet Explorer), and whether the user responded to the advertisement delivered. 

VNCentral' use of the non-personally identifiable information collected by VNCentral' advertising agency may include targeting advertisements and measuring advertisement effectiveness.

**PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION**  
Personally identifiable information about our visitors is collected only when knowingly and voluntarily submitted by those visitors. VNCentral uses such information only for the purpose for which it was submitted, unless we disclose other uses at the time of collection. VNCentral does not sell personal information to third parties. VNCentral may share personally identifiable information with other parts of our company, but this will never be used on an individual basis outside of the company. VNCentral maintains appropriate safeguards to ensure the security, integrity, and privacy of personally identifiable information in its possession. VNCentral may use such personally identifiable information in the aggregate (non-identifiable) form to make our Web Sites better and more responsive to the needs of our visitors. This statistical compilation of non-identifiable information may also be used by or provided to others for marketing, advertising, or research purposes. 

**LINKS TO OTHER SITES**  
VNCentral chooses its advertisers and business partners carefully. However, VNCentral is not responsible for the content or privacy practices of Web Sitess operated by third parties that are linked to or from our Web Sites. These links are meant for the visitor's convenience only. Links to third party Web Sitess do not constitute sponsorship, endorsement, or approval by VNCentral of content, policies or practices of such Sitess. Once you have left the VNCentral Web Sites via such a link, you should check the applicable privacy policy of the third party Sites. VNCentral may also be linked to Web Sitess operated by companies affiliated with VNCentral. Visitors to those Sitess should refer to their separate privacy policies and practices. 

**CHAT ROOMS, MESSAGE BOARDS AND SUBMISSIONS**  
Should any visitor to VNCentral Web Sites provide information, questions, comments, suggestions, reviews or any material through the feedback mechanisms located in the Web Sites, VNCentral shall have no obligation of any kind with respect to such information and shall be free to reproduce, use, disclose and distribute the information to others without limitation. The information expressed in any Message Boards or chat rooms, or other forums conducted on VNCentral, if any, are not necessarily those of VNCentral or its affiliated or related entities or content providers and VNCentral makes no representations or warranties regarding that information or those opinions.

* _****The above information will be change without any further notice._
